A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Welfare Interests - General Files, Series P FA325
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Negro Organizations
  - Negro Organizations - Miscellaneous Work Among Negroes - Day Nursery for Colored Children, Harlem, 1942-1943 (Box 32, Folder 351)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller contributed in 1943, but later appeals were declined.
  - Negro Organizations - Miscellaneous Work Among Negroes - Harlem Council on Social Hygiene, 1945-1948 (Box 32, Folder 352)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd gave $3,500 in 1945.
  - Negro Organizations - Negro Questions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Interest, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 353)
    A few examples of policy-making procedures from John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s office are presented here. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
    111.1A
  - Negro Organizations - Riverdale Children's Association, 1936-1941 (Box 33, Folder 354)
    The Association's name was changed in 1944 from "Colored Orphan Asylum," when it was no longer restricted to Negroes. This represented a switch to foster-home orientation. Here are reports on finances, board disputes, etc. There were regular family and Rockefeller Brothers Fund contributions from 1940 to 1957, ranging from $1,000 to $3,500 annually. Correspondents include Marshall Field, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Winthrop Rockefeller.
    111.2
  - Negro Organizations - Riverdale Children's Association, 1942-1946 (Box 33, Folder 355)
    See also Box 57, Folder 638.
  - Negro Organizations - Riverdale Children's Association, 1942-1946 (Box 33, Folder 0355A)
  - Negro Organizations - Riverdale Children's Association, 1946-1961 (Box 33, Folder 356)
  - Negro Organizations - Katy Ferguson House, 1913-1953 (Box 33, Folder 357)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave heavily and regularly.
    111.3
  - Negro Organizations - Empire Friendly Shelter, 1915-1920 (Box 33, Folder 358)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed in 1917 and 1918 but had no personal interest in the project.
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League, 1939-1948 (Box 33, Folder 359)
    Winthrop Rockefeller was very active in this organization. The family contributed and received reports on the League's work. Here are criticisms of the organization's set-up and comments on Lester Granger. Correspondents include Winthrop Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Lester B. Granger.
    111.4
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League, 1948-1952 (Box 33, Folder 360)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League, 1953-1961 (Box 33, Folder 361)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League, 1955-1961 (Box 33, Folder 0361A)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Contributions, 1921-1930 (Box 33, Folder 362)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave toward the Industrial Work of the League. The Davison Fund gave gifts. John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, and Winthrop Rockefeller also contributed. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller.
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Contributions, 1924-1944 (Box 34, Folder 363)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Contributions, 1944-1961 (Box 34, Folder 364)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Contributions - New Headquarters Building, 1952-1957 (Box 34, Folder 365)
    Winthrop Rockefeller gave $100,000 toward purchase of the building.
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Family Exhibit, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 366)
    A selection of family-owned paintings was put on exhibit to raise funds for the League. Correspondents include Winthrop Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Abby Rockefeller Mauz, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Family Exhibit, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 367)
  - Negro Organizations - National Urban League - Printed Material, 1947-1959 (Box 34, Folder 368)
    In this folder are clippings on Winthrop Rockefeller's League activities. Correspondents include Winthrop Rockefeller.
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League, 1921-1936 (Box 34, Folder 369)
    This League chapter dealt with social, welfare, and industrial work in Harlem and the violent conflicts within and between Harlem agencies during the Depression. There is a 1934 Survey and reorganization plan along with the documentation of changes of personnel and plans for merger with the Brooklyn Urban League. In 1944 the merger took place to create the new League of Greater New York. Contributions were made by the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial Fund, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, and Laurance S. Rockefeller.
    111.41
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League, 1937-1944 (Box 34, Folder 370)
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League, 1938-1941 (Box 34, Folder 0370A)
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions - March 16, 1928 Pledge to Building Fund, 1928-1930 (Box 34, Folder 371)
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions - February 28, 1929 Pledge, 1929-1932 (Box 34, Folder 372)
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions - April 1932 (Box 35, Folder 373)
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions - May 1933 (Box 35, Folder 374)
    See also Box 56, Folder 628.
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions, 1936-1944 (Box 35, Folder 375)
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League of Greater New York, 1944-1960 (Box 35, Folder 376)
    Consolidation of the New York Urban League, the Brooklyn League on Urban Conditions and the Lincoln Settlement Association. John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributed. Discussion of the League's activities. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel.
    111.42
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League of Greater New York, 1949-1955 (Box 35, Folder 0376A)
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League Service Fund, 1945-1954 (Box 35, Folder 377)
    The Fund collected money for both local and national Urban Leagues. Here are studies of the organization of the Leagues and appeals for participation in its campaigns. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Arthur Jones, Winthrop Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel.
    111.43
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League Service Fund - Contributions, 1945-1960 (Box 35, Folder 378)
    Contributions were made to funds for the work of national and local urban leagues. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller.
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League of Westchester County, Inc., 1941-1958 (Box 35, Folder 379)
    The work of the League is described. All appeals were declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    111.44
  - Negro Organizations - Urban League of Westchester County, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 35, Folder 0379A)
  - Negro Organizations - Brooklyn Urban League, 1922-1943 (Box 35, Folder 380)
    Annual contributions of $1,000 were made, as well as routine gifts. The Brooklyn League merged into the Urban League of Greater New York in 1944. correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Willard S. Richardson, Thomas B. Appleget.
    111.5
  - Negro Organizations - Brooklyn Urban League - Contributions, 1932-1944 (Box 35, Folder 381)
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1927-1939 (Box 35, Folder 382)
    Rockefeller advisors were divided over the policies and personnel of the NAACP. They saw the necessity of the legal approach but in general preferred education and gradualism as solutions to the race problem. Here is information on lynching, the influence of the Communist Party among Negroes, and the history of the NAACP. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed from 1928 to 1939. Nelson A. Rockefeller contributed in 1951, 1956, and 1959 and was a Life Member. Correspondents include W.E.B DuBois, James Weldon Johnson, Jackson B. Davis, Walter White, W. Alexander, Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    111.6
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1940-1961 (Box 36, Folder 383)
    See also Box 56, Folder 634.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1951-1960 (Box 36, Folder 0383A)
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - James Weldon Johnson, 1930-1940 (Box 36, Folder 384)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd corresponded with Mr. Johnson.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1932-1942 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributed annually, 1932-1941, and made a final contribution in 1958.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1942-1957 (Box 36, Folder 386)
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Clippings, 1944-1960 (Box 36, Folder 387)
    Clippings about NAACP activities were selected.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Contributions, 1930-1961 (Box 36, Folder 388)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed, 1928-1951.
    See also Box 57, Folder 641.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Contributions, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 388A)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted Material
  - Negro Organizations - Committee of 100, 1944-1961 (Box 36, Folder 389)
    The committee of whites was dedicated to an "America of Justice and Equality for our Negro fellow citizens" and was a branch of the NAACP. All appeals were declined. Correspondents include Dana S. Creel, Arthur W. Packard.
    111.61
  - Negro Organizations - Gulfside Association, Waveland, Mississippi, 1927-1934 (Box 36, Folder 390)
    There was a summer camp for Negro religious work in the Gulf region. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $35,000 between 1928 and 1933. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, R. Jones.
    111.7
  - Negro Organizations - Gulfside Association, Waveland, Mississippi - Pledge and Payment, 1928-1933 (Box 36, Folder 391)
  - Negro Organizations - Association for the Study of Negro Life, 1926-1953 (Box 37, Folder 392)
    Appeals were made for funds to study the history of Negroes, but they were consistently denied. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Thomas B. Appleget.
    111.8
  - Negro Organizations - Institute for Colored Ministers, 1930-1934 (Box 37, Folder 393)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. supported the Institute.
    111.9
  - Negro Organizations - Forest Neighborhood House, 1945-1951 (Box 37, Folder 394)
    This Bronx community center was originally set up for Jewish residents but was converted to Negro use in 1945. Nelson A. Rockefeller contributed in 1946 and John D. Rockefeller 3rd contributed in 1949. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Nelson A. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    111.11
  - Negro Organizations - West 110th Street Community Center, 1946-1950 (Box 37, Folder 395)
    The Negro and Puerto Rican center began operation in 1947 but closed for lack of funds in 1949. There was never any Rockefeller interest. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur Jones.
    111.12
  - Negro Organizations - Committee on Unity, 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 396)
    New York City's mayor devised this committee on Negro problems, which reported on racial problems in the city. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined the Committee's request to be its chairman, but he did contribute to its work. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Fiorello H. LaGuardia.
    111.13
  - Negro Organizations - Committee on Unity, 1946-1949 (Box 37, Folder 397)
  - Negro Organizations - Committee on Unity, 1949-1954 (Box 37, Folder 398)
  - Negro Organizations - Committee on Unity, 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 0398A)
  - Negro Organizations - American Council on Race Relations, 1944-1949 (Box 37, Folder 399)
    The council developed out of the Chicago Conference. The Rockefeller office watched the growth of the Council, but John D. Rockefeller, Jr. declined all invitations and appeals for contributions. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard.
    111.14
  - Negro Organizations - American Council on Race Relations, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 0399A)
  - Negro Organizations - National Council of Negro Women, 1945-1960 (Box 37, Folder 400)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller contributed in 1945 and 1954. Winthrop Rockefeller contributed in 1955. Correspondents include Nelson A. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller.
    111.16
  - Negro Organizations - Legal Size Material (Box 55, Folder 621)
    Folders 350-394.
  - Negro Organizations - New York Urban League - Contributions - May 1933 (Box 56, Folder 628)
    Graph of Growth of Contribution from 1921 to 1932.
    Removed from Box 35, Folder 374.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 2 articles (Box 56, Folder 634)
    White, Walter. "How Washington's Color Line Looks to Me," "The Saturday Evening Post," July 18, 1954. White, Walter. "How Detroit Fights Race Hatred," "The Saturday Evening Post," July 18, 1953.
    Removed from Box 36, Folder 383.
  - Negro Organizations - Miscellaneous Work Among Negroes (Box 56, Folder 635)
    "Princeton Church Calls White Minister," "Ebony" Magazine, June 1957.
    Removed from Box 32, Folder 350.
  - Negro Organizations - Riverdale Children's Association (Box 57, Folder 638)
    Income and Expenditures, 1929-1940.
    Removed from Box 33, Folder 355.
  - Negro Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) - Contributions (Box 57, Folder 641)
    Chart of NAACP Statement of Income and Expenses, 1935-1938.
    Removed from Box 36, Folder 388.
- Prisons and Prisoners
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Association of New York, 1901-1956 (Box 37, Folder 401)
    John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and John D. Rockefeller 3rd all contributed. Other family members and boards gave gifts, but there was no real personal interest. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    59
  - Prisons and Prisoners - National Committee on Prison Labor, 1916-1941 (Box 37, Folder 402)
    The Committee studied Canadian internment policies during World War I. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed one third of the cost. Some small contributions were made later, but there was little interest in general. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, Thomas B. Appleget, Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard.
    59.1
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Voluntary Defenders Committee, 1916-1922 (Box 38, Folder 403)
    The organization was intended to provide legal aid to the needy. It united with the Legal Aid Society in 1920. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed to its costs from 1917 to 1920. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, J. B. Reynolds.
    59.3
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations, 1916-1957 (Box 38, Folder 404)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. contributed to various rehabilitation activities, but most appeals for aid were declined.
    59.4
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - Welfare League Association, 1922-1938 (Box 38, Folder 405)
    Annual gifts were given.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - American Prison Association, 1918-1933 (Box 38, Folder 406)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made a few small contributions.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - National Society for Penal Information, 1922-1931 (Box 38, Folder 407)
    Annual contributions of $500 to $3,000 were given.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - League of Another Chance, 1925-1934 (Box 38, Folder 408)
    $250 was given annually from 1925-1931.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - Committee for Securing Employment for Ex-Prisoners, 1929-1932 (Box 38, Folder 409)
    One $500 give was given.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - E. E. Dudding, Prisoners' Relief Society, 1927-1954 (Box 38, Folder 410)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Prison Reform Associations - The Brotherhood Club, Cleveland, 1910 (Box 38, Folder 411)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Osborne Association, 1937-1949 (Box 38, Folder 412)
    The Association worked for the rehabilitation of criminals. John D. Rockefeller 3rd investigated their work. Abby Aldrich Rockefeller contributed. Correspondents include Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    59.2
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Osborne Association, 1937-1949 (Box 38, Folder 0412A)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Osborne Association - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1939-1952 (Box 38, Folder 413)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Osborne Association - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1946-1948 (Box 38, Folder 0413A)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Osborne Association - David Rockefeller, 1941-1961 (Box 38, Folder 414)
    David Rockefeller made annual contributions. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, David Rockefeller.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Young Men's Vocational Foundation, Inc., 1941-1961 (Box 38, Folder 415)
    Nelson A. Rockefeller made contribution. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    59.6
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Young Men's Vocational Foundation, Inc., 1941-1961 (Box 38, Folder 415A)
  - Prisons and Prisoners - Young Men's Vocational Foundation, Inc. - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Contributions, 1939-1947 (Box 38, Folder 416)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd made one contribution in 1940 but all other appeals were declined.
  - Prisons and Prisoners - National Probation Association, 1922-1955 (Box 38, Folder 417)
    All appeals were declined. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard.
    121.1
  - Prisons and Prisoners and Prohibition and Alcoholism - Legal Size Material (Box 55, Folder 622)
    Folders 401-470.
- Prohibition and Alcoholism
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition, 1909-1931 (Box 39, Folder 418)
    Here are comments on prohibition. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. chided the Sheriffs Jury for serving liquor at its banquet. Plans for liquor control after appeal are discussed. The Rockefeller Brothers Fund made contributions to the National Council on Alcoholism. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Raymond B. Fosdick, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
    24
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition, 1932-1942 (Box 39, Folder 419)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition, 1948-1960 (Box 39, Folder 420)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Anti-Prohibition, 1922-1937 (Box 39, Folder 421)
    Appeals for contributions toward repeal were declined.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1919-1957 (Box 39, Folder 422)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - National Temperance Bureau, 1920-1929 (Box 39, Folder 423)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $2,500.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Native Races Anti-Liquor Committee, 1916-1932 (Box 39, Folder 424)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Intercollegiate Prohibition Association, 1924-1943 (Box 39, Folder 425)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $10,000.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Social Science Research Council, 1926-1928 (Box 39, Folder 426)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gave $16,000 for a study of the effects of the Eighteenth Amendment.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - H. D. Taft, Liquor Law Pamphlet, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 427)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. approved.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Prohibition - Westchester County Prohibitory Union, 1899-1913 (Box 39, Folder 428)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Crusaders, Inc., 1932-1946 (Box 39, Folder 429)
    The Crusaders was an organization to secure the repeal of the Eighteenth Amendment and promote true temperance. It swung to an anti-New Deal position in 1934. The family did not contribute. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Women's National Committee for Law Enforcement, 1923-1933 (Box 39, Folder 430)
    The Committee intended to create public opinion favoring enforcement of the Volstead Act among women. Abby Aldrich Rockefeller spoke at the Convention, representing the Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA). John D. Rockefeller, Jr. made several contributions through his Special Advisory Committee. Correspondents include Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur Woods, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller.
    24.1
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - Citizens Committee of One Thousand, 1923-1959 (Box 39, Folder 431)
    The Committee held nationwide conferences on the enforcement of the Volstead Act. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. was a member and contributed about 10% of its annual budget from 1923-1928. He visited President Coolidge. After 1928 there was no more active participation. Correspondents include Arthur Woods, Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Fred B. Smith.
    24.2
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Clippings, 1932-1946 (Box 40, Folder 432)
    The clippings represent those for and against the statement.
    24.3
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Copies of Statement (Box 40, Folder 433)
    Here are fifteen printed copies.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with Reply (A-C) (Box 40, Folder 434)
    There are many interesting comments, including those from E. M. Hopkins, Calvin Coolidge, and others.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with Reply (D-J) (Box 40, Folder 435)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with Reply (K-P) (Box 40, Folder 436)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with Reply (R-Z) (Box 40, Folder 437)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with Suggestions, 1932-1933 (Box 40, Folder 438)
    Most of these letters include plans for repeal or temperance.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Club Approvals (Box 40, Folder 439)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Miscellaneous Letters with Reply (Box 40, Folder 440)
    These letters include suggestions about temperance and prohibition. Some also contain requests for aid.
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Opposition with Reply (A-L), 1932-1944 (Box 40, Folder 441)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Opposition with Reply (M-Z), 1932-1944 (Box 41, Folder 442)
  - Prohibition and Alcoholism - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Statement, June 6, 1932 - Letters of Approval with No Response (Box 41, Folder 443)